mom: how's it going [pregnant] man
dad: oh yeah too easy man don't know [what all the fuss is about]
-- 媽：[懷孕]怎麼樣
爸：哦耶 太簡單了，不知道有什麼好[大驚小怪]
媽：好吧
mom: oh good, well soon you'll start feeling the baby kicking
dad: oh no I'm sure that's not for [a little while], ow
-- 媽：很快你就會開始感覺到寶寶在踢腿
爸：哦，不，我確定這不會持續[一段時間], 噢...
kick kick kick
-- 踢踢踢
mom: oh you never forget that [first kick]
dad: okay that's a [wrap] kids come on unclip
-- 媽：哦，你永遠不會忘記[第一腳]
爸：好吧，這只是一個 [背巾], 孩子, 來幫忙[解開]
bluey: no not yet you haven't had the baby
-- 布麗：不，你還沒有生孩子
dad: too bad how do you get this thing off
bluey: you said if you're going to do something, [do it properly]
-- 爸：太糟糕了，你怎麼把這東西弄下來
布麗：你說如果你打算做某件事，就會[把它做對]
dad: ah that [advice] doesn't apply to me bingo: hello
-- 爸：噢，那個[建議]不適用於我
賓果：哈囉
bluey: he's having a baby
-- 布麗：他有孩子了
bluey: what happens now
dad: what are you asking me for? aren't you the [midwife]
bluey: no I'm just a friend
-- 布麗：現在發生了什麼？
爸：妳問我做什麼？妳不是助產士嗎？
布麗：不，我只是一個朋友
bluey: I  work at a [petrol station]
dad: what
bingo: I'm coming out
dad: well who's gonna [deliver my baby]
-- 布麗：我在[加油站]工作。
爸：什麼？
賓果：我要出來了。
爸：好吧，誰要來[接生我的孩子]
neighbor: true blue, is it me and you? is it mum and dad? is it...
buley: er lucky star can you [give us a hand] with something
neighbor: yeah [no worries] bluey
-- 鄰居：我真的很憂鬱, 是我和你嗎？是媽媽和爸爸嗎？是... (註：John Williams 的 True Blue 歌詞）
布麗：呃，幸運星，你能[幫我們]嗎
鄰居：[不用擔心]，布麗
I didn't know this was the something dad:[lighten up] pat
neighbor: but I don't know how to deliver a baby
-- 鄰居：我不知道這是什麼東西
爸：[放輕鬆], pat
鄰居：但我不知道如何接生
dad: I thought you [grew up] in a farm neighbor: we [grew sorghum]
neighbor's son: dad the [cricket] started
-- 爸：我以為你是在農場[長大]
鄰居：我們[種高梁]
鄰居兒子：爸爸，[板球]遊戲開始了
neighbor: I'm busy mate just shout if there's a wicket
neighbor's son: okay
neighbor: well how hard can this be? I'll just gravel it
-- 鄰居：我在忙，如果擊住三柱門再叫我
鄰居兒子：OK
鄰居：好吧，這能有多難？讓我來鏟除它
neighbor: hey where are you going
bingo: I'm not going anywhere
dad: bingo that [tickles]
neighbor: well we'll see about that, i've got a foot
-- 鄰居：嘿，你要去哪裡
賓果：我哪兒也不去
爸：賓果，那樣很[癢]
鄰居：好，我們來看看，我捉到一隻腳了
dad: ooh she's got my belly hair
-- 爸：喔，她捉到我肚子的毛了
neighbor's son: it's none for six dad neighbor: any boundaries
neighbor's son: one boundary two singles
neighbor: who got the boundary
buley & dad: focus oh
neighbor: oh, yeah, sorry
-- 鄰居兒子：現在零比六了，爸爸
鄰居：有任何長打嗎？
鄰居兒子：一個2分的長打
鄰居：誰打的長打
布麗和爸爸：專心點
鄰居：喔，抱歉
neighbor: I can see the [butt] I can see the butt
-- 鄰居：我可以看到[屁股]我可以看到屁股
host: you can watch lots more bluey on BBC iPlayer ask your grown-up to search bluey
-- 主持人：你可以在 BBC iPlayer 上，看到更多布麗，請你家中的大人搜索 bluey
--